Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2000; 15 Linear Feet 22 boxes containing 458 items.
  - New York University Class Lectures, 1999
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0170)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0171)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0172)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0173)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0174)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0175)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0176)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0177)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0178)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0179)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette, 1999 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0180)
    - Politics of Cruelty, Lectures 1-12 [incomplete], circa 1999
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0181)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0182)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0183)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0184)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0185)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0186)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0187)
    - Literature and Social Class, Lectures 2-8 [incomplete], 2000 Spring
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0188)
    - Angela's Ashes, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0189)
    - Angela's Ashes, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0190)
    - Dorothy Alison, Bastard Out of Carolina, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0191)
    - NYU Law School, Inquisition/Impeachment, Feb. 8, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0192)
    - Seminar on academy as sweatshop, 1999
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0193)
    - 2nd seminar, adjunct exploitation, 1999 Apr. 20, 1999 April 20
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0194)
    - Seminar, last part, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0195)
  - Public Appearances, 1974-1999
    - 1974 Oct. 11, Sex and Literature, Johns Hopkins University, 1974 October 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0196)
    - 1975 Apr. 17, Sex and Literature, Univ. of California Santa Cruz, 1975 April 17
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0197)
    - 1975 Apr. 18, UCSC, 1975 April 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0198)
    - 1976 Oct., Wisconsin Women in the Arts, Kate Millett and Judy Chicago, 1976 October
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0199)
    - 1976 Oct., Wisconsin Women in the Arts, Kate Millett and Judy Chicago, 1976 October
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0200)
    - 1977 Feb. 23, Lesbians and Literature, SUNY-Stonybrook, 1977 February 23
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0201)
    - 1978 Nov. 25, Keynote Address, Fifth National Convention of the Gay Academic Union, Los Angeles, 1978 November 25
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0202)
    - 1978 Nov. 25, Keynote Address, Fifth National Convention of the Gay Academic Union, Los Angeles, 1978 November 25
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0203)
    - 1979 Feb. 16, Reading, Rachel Ackerman benefit, 1979 February 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0204)
    - 1979 Apr. 11, On Lessing, Lewis and Clark, 1979 April 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0205)
    - 1981 Feb. 15, Poetry reading, 1981 February 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0206)
    - 1981 Sept., Workshop, West Coast Music Festival
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0207)
    - 1984 Apr. 10, Reading The Loony-Bin Trip, Different Light Bookstore, 1984 April 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0208)
    - 1984 Apr. 30, On Autobiography, Kate teaches at LeMoyne, 1984 April 30
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0209)
    - 1984 Summer, Reading "Aunt Dorothy," the Farm
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0210)
    - 1985 Jan., Lunacy and Sex Roles, Temple Univ., 1985 January
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0211)
    - 1986 May 18, Reading, Farm benefit
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0212)
    - 1988, National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA speech)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0213)
    - 1990 May 23-24, 2 radio interviews, San Francisco
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0214)
    - 1990 May 25, Transcribe this - Kate at Berkeley for Sally
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0215)
    - 1990 May, Loony-Bin Trip speech to Radical Therapists, San Francisco
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0216)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0216_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0216_02.wav)
    - 1990 May, Loony-Bin Trip interview with Claire Marks, San Mateo
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0217)
    - 1990 Oct. 18, Address to peer advocates, Syracuse, and Paul Simon, 1990 October 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0218)
    - 1990, The Loony-Bin Trip - NARPA convention, Miami Lakes, Fla.
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0219)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0219_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0219_02.wav)
    - 1992 Feb. 16, The Loony-Bin Trip interview with Erickson Kiva, M.S.U., Lansing, 1992 February 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0220)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0220_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0220_02.wav)
    - 1993 Apr. 15, Kate at Bologna, Palazzo dei Notari for Women's Center, 1993 April 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0221)
    - 1993 Apr. 16, Bologna interview with Noi Donne, 1993 April 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0222)
    - 1993 Aug. 24, interview on monogamy, 1993 August 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0223)
    - 1993 Oct. 18, Kate and Mary Jane at Amazon Bookstore, reading Loony-Bin Trip and Aunt Mig, Minneapolis, 1993 October 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0224)
    - 1994 May 9, Jim Bohannon Show
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0225)
    - 1995 Oct. 3, Women's Consortium radio program, 1995 October 3
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV6, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0226)
    - 1995 Oct. 16, Dalhousie Student Union Building, 1995 October 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0227)
    - 1995 Oct. 16, Dalhousie Student Union Building, 1995 October 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0228)
    - 1997 Mar. 7, CUNY conference, 1997 March 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0229)
    - 1997 Mar. 7, CUNY conference, 1997 March 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0230)
    - 1999 Mar. 1, U.S. and International Feminism, Univ. Texas - San Antonio, 1999 March 1
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0231)
    - Undated, Kate on radio, Basement
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0232)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0232_01.wav)
    - Undated, Kate - Tallahassee
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0233)
    - Undated, Kate Millett [from Gul Seden Wines, Italian Radio]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0234)
    - Undated, Kate at APA
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0235)
    - Undated, Kate reads on Long Island, Flying, Loony-Bin Trip, A.D.
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0236)
    - Undated, Kate reading to herself for LeMoyne, Elegy #2, Loony Bin, Prolyxn
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0237)
    - Undated, Kate on Art, Univ. Missouri
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0238)
    - Undated, Kate reads Basement/ Sita
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0239)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0239_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0239_02.wav)
    - Undated, Prison Women's Benefit
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0240)
    - Undated, Kate on Lesbian Lit/Kate reading Flying, Bryn Mawr
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0241)
    - Undated, Oxford symposium I
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0242)
    - Undated, Kate and NY Times/Bugging phone
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0243)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0243_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0243_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate reads Gertrude Stein/Kate reads Autobiography Alice B. Tokley
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0244)
  - Second Floor Salon Recordings, 1980-1981
    - 1980 Jan. 10, Kate reads Going to Iran, 1980 January 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0245)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0245_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0245_02.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 9, Kate reads Elegy for Sita, 1981 January 9
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0246)
    - 1981 Jan. 9, Kate reads Elegy for Sita, 1981 January 9
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0247)
    - 1981 Jan. 10, Kate reads Going to Iran, 1981 January 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0248)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0248_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0248_02.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 10, Kate reads Going to Iran, 1981 January 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0249)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0249_01.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 10, Kate reads Going to Iran, 1981 January 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0250)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0250_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0250_02.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 10, Kate reads Going to Iran, 1981 January 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0251)
  - Personal or Unidentified, 1973-1999
    - 1973 Sept. 30, Diary 1 and 2
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0252)
    - 1979 Mar. 7, Translation and Pro. Burn, 1979 March 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0253)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0253_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0253_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 28, Kate trying to sing, 1979 March 28
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0254)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0254_01.wav)
    - Circa 1979, Playing
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0255)
    - 1979 July 18, Kate, The Basement, the Farm
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0256)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0256_01.wav)
    - 1980 Mar. 24, Mother M.'s Eyes, Bugged phone, 1980 March 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0257)
    - 1980 July 25, Art stroll with Alex/Kate tells lithium
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0258)
    - 1980 July 26, Kim's lesson in reality
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0259)
    - 1980 July, Behind My Back, Teresa/Abortive tape
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0260)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0260_01.wav)
    - 1980 Sept. 20, The Bowery, The Last Bust
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0261)
    - Circa 1980s, Me and Witch [removed from notes on torture book]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV7, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0262)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0262_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0262_02.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 15, Eros and Pornography, 1981 January 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0263)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0263_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0263_02.wav)
    - 1981 Jan. 15, Eros and Pornography, 1981 January 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0264)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0264_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0264_02.wav)
    - 1987 Oct., Jill Johnston and Kate, 1987 October
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0265)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0265_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0265_02.wav)
    - 1987 Oct., Jill Johnston and Kate, 1987 October
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0266)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0266_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0266_02.wav)
    - 1987 Oct., Jill Johnston and Kate, 1987 October
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0267)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0267_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0267_02.wav)
    - 1988 Mar. 7, Dinner at Jill's, Jill Johnston and Ingrid, 1988 March 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0268)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0268_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0268_02.wav)
    - 1988 Apr. 5, Dinner with Alma and Julie, 1988 April 5
      - Tape 1, original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0269)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0269_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0269_02.wav)
      - Tape 2, original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0421)
    - 1993 Apr. 24, Kate on Mother, Minnesota, 1993 April 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0270)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0270_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0270_02.wav)
    - 1999, Valdosta, Georgia, Int'l feminism
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0271)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0271_01.wav)
    - Undated, Kate and the Black Scholar (cont'd)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0272)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0272_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0272_02.wav)
    - Undated, Black Irish vs. Bourgeoisie Black Scholar
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0273)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0273_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0273_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate on Michael X
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0274)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0274_01.wav)
    - Undated, "Irish Night"
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0275)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0275_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0275_02.wav)
    - Undated, "Irish Night"
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0276)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0276_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0276_02.wav)
    - Undated, "Irish Night"
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0277)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0277_01.wav)
    - Undated, "Irish Night"
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0278)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0278_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0278_02.wav)
    - Undated, Me and Ti-Grace after Colgate
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0279)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0279_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0279_02.wav)
    - Undated, Dinner July 25 Fri. nite [sic]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0280)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0280_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0280_02.wav)
    - Undated, Tape Hannelore, Kate prepares her show and listens to jazz radio
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0281)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0281_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0281_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate Klass Women Writers
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0282)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0282_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0282_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate and women in Berlin
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0283)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0283_01.wav)
    - Undated, Kate and women in Berlin
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0284)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0284_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0284_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate talking about The Basement
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0285)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0285_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0285_02.wav)
    - Undated, Kate reading "Iran"
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0286)
    - Undated, Kate reads Loony-Bin book to Sophie and Skip - Fumio divorce
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0287)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0287_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0287_02.wav)
    - Undated, Identify [conference panel on gender]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0288)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0288_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0288_02.wav)
    - Undated, Way to Folsom
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0289)
    - Undated, Sigrid
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0290)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0290_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0290_02.wav)
    - Undated, ?something [unidentified woman, mostly background noise]